let quiz   =[
    {question: "The expression '4xy+7' is in",
option:[
    "One variable ",
    "Two variable",
    "No variable",
    "None of these",

],
answer:2, 
},

{
    question: "The expression 'x+y+z' is in" ,
option:[
    "One variable ",
    "Two variable",
    "No variable",
    "Three variable",


],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "The generalised form of the number 52 is",
option:[
    "10X5+2",
    "100X5+2",
    "10X2+5",
    "10X5",


],
answer:1, 
},
{question: "The number '10X7+5' in usual form is ",
option:[
    57,
    75,
    55,
    77,

],
answer:2, 
},

{
    question: "A horse eats 18 kg of carrots in 12 days? how much does he eat in 9 days",
option:[
    "11.5 kg",
    "14.5 kg",
    "12.5 kg",
    "13.5 kg",

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "10 metres of cloth Rs. 1000. What will 4 metres cost?",
option:[
    "Rs. 800",
    "Rs. 200",
    "Rs. 400",
    "Rs. 100 ",

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "Which is the following numbers is not  a perfect cube?",
option:[
    1331,
    512,
    343,
    100,

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "Which is the following numbers is a perfect cube?" ,
option:[
    125,
    36,
    75,
    100,


],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "Between 30 and 40, the perfect square number is",
option:[
    36,
    35,
    34,
    "None",

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "The perfect square number out of '2','3','4' and '5' is",
option:[
    2,
    3,
    4,
    5,

    
],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "a+b=b+a is called",
option:[
    "Commutative law of addition",
    "Associative law of addition",
    "Distributive law of addition",
    "None of these",

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "The number of sides in a regular polygon is 15, then meaasure of each exterior angle is",
option:[
    "18 degree",
    "36 degree",
    "20 degree",
    "24 degree",

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "The sum of the measures of all the four angles of a quadrilateral is",
option:[
    "90 degree",
    "180 degree",
    "360 degree",
    "720 degree",

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "0 is not",
option:[
    "A natural number",
    "A whole number",
    "An integer",    
    "A rational number",

],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "When 9 is added to two times a number,we get 67.The number is ",
option:[
    28,
    29,
    24,
    14,

],
answer:2, 
}]